cram.com 2003-04-13

# Permacharts.com

**Privacy Policy**

We believe that your personal information deserves protection. While you can visit the "website" without registering or providing any personal information, you will need to register if you want to make a purchase. 

We may also use personal account information and data collected through your personal identification to generate statistics and aggregate reports for internal use and for sharing with affiliates, subsidiaries, licensees, successors and advertisers. These statistics and aggregate reports will not contain any personally identifiable information. Your identity is kept anonymous. 

When you provide us with personal information or place an order, it's done through a secure server. One of today's most advanced security systems -- Secure Socket Layers (SSL) -- encrypts all information you provide before sending it to our own server. Only when it reaches our servers is your information decrypted. 

Permacharts, Inc. reserves the right to co-operate with local, provincial and national officials in any investigation requiring either personal information -- including any personal information provided online -- or reports about lawful or unlawful user activities on the Web Site. 

Permacharts, Inc. reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. We also reserve the right at any time to disclose any information in an individual's account:   
i. to satisfy any law, regulation or government request;   
ii. if such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to site operation; or   
iii. to protect the rights or property of Permacharts, Inc. and its users, sponsors, providers, licensors or merchants.
